crownrelo.com 2016-03-28

# Privacy Policy | Crown Relocations

The CROWN WORLDWIDE GROUP and all its subsidiaries comply with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Crown Worldwide Group has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Crown Worldwide Group’s certification, please visit [www.export.gov/safeharbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor).

The CROWN WORLDWIDE GROUP has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the following websites:

These sites contain links to other sites. CROWN WORLDWIDE GROUP is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such linked websites. Users should check the applicable Privacy Policy of such websites when providing personally identifiable information on those linked websites.

CROWN WORLDWIDE GROUP does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, an On-line Service Request requires the collection of personal data in order for us to be able to respond promptly and correctly to the service request.

CROWN WORLDWIDE GROUP reserves the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site.

###  Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access

Visitors can access our website home page and browse our site without disclosing personal data by disabling the cookie settings on our website.

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records, public bodies or private organizations.

###  Automatic Collection of Information

We use cookies on this website to store information on your computer or mobile device. Cookies are small text files which help us understand how this website is being used. They let you navigate between pages efficiently, remember your preferences, and generally improve your browsing experience. Cookies can also help ensure marketing you see on-line is more relevant to you. More information about cookies can be found in our Cookie Policy.

To give you the very best browsing experience, the cookie settings on this website are set to allow all cookies. If you continue to browse this site without changing these settings, you consent to this. If you want to change your settings at any time, please click the Adjust Cookie Settings link at the bottom of our web pages.

This site uses DoubleClick's remarketing pixels and Google Analytics cookies. These cookies are part of the web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

To opt out of DoubleClick's use of cookies and remarketing pixels, click [here](http://www.google.com/settings/ads?hl=en) to opt-out or go to the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out [page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) for additional information.

Information about cookies

Additional useful information about cookies can be found at: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

We may also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website.

###  Privacy Compliance

Our Privacy Policy is compliant with the following instrument: International Safe Harbor Privacy Principles. In order to demonstrate that our Privacy Policy accords with the above privacy instrument, we are voluntarily committed to a self-assessment procedure.

###  Privacy Support

CROWN WORLDWIDE GROUP’s Privacy Policy has been developed out of respect for the privacy preferences and choices of our customers and prospects. We have established procedures to ensure that every reasonable effort is made to address your concerns. CROWN WORLDWIDE GROUP has designated two privacy officials to implement our Customer Privacy Policy for its respective customers and prospects. You should find contact information on each of our business unit’s websites that collect data from you.

If you have an inquiry or concern about our Privacy Policy, please contact:  
 **Nelson Akinrinade, Esq.**  
Group Compliance Officer  
10421 Sanden Drive  
Dallas, TX 75238  
United States

**Phone:**  +1 214 341 2371  
 **Fax:** +1 214 341 3160  
 **Email:**[nakinrinade@crownww.com](mailto:nakinrinade@crownww.com)  
 **Website:**[www.crownworldwide.com](https://www.crownworldwide.com/)

**Chris Davis-Pipe**  
Group Vice President of Information Technology  
Crown Worldwide Holdings Ltd.  
Suite 2001, MassMutual Tower  
38 Gloucester Road  
Wanchai, Hong Kong

**Phone:**  +852 2876 2623  
 **Fax:**  +852 2528 0177  
 **Email:**[cdavispipe@crownww.com](mailto:cdavispipe@crownww.com)  
 **website:** [www.crownworldwide.com](https://www.crownworldwide.com/)

The foregoing policies are effective as of August 1 2012. CROWN WORLDWIDE GROUP reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
